[indistinct chatter]
[footfall]
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[MALE STUDENT 5A]
Whoa, it's Serina!
[MALE STUDENT 5B]
Blessed sight this morning.
She's such a damn cutie!
[MALE STUDENT 5A]
You mean knockout!
Hey, you should talk to her!
[MALE STUDENT 5B]
Uh! Nah.
Not messin'
with those groupies.
[UKA]
Serina Kanno.
To some...
she plays the role of an idol
or a model.
And...
[YASUSHI] Oh, yeah, didn't
she and Kai used to go out?
-[MIRU] Really?
-[UKA]...to Miura,
-an ex-girlfriend.
-[indistinct chatter]
[AYUMI] They dated
in year three of junior high,
but they broke up
outta the blue,
and it's been super awkward
between them ever since.
Even I don't know why!
[UKA]
It's that bad?
Then, that means...
[SERINA] And I so
appreciate you catching it!
Thanks again!
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
Even though she's amazing,
it wasn't enough for him.
[indistinct chatter]
♪
SPARKLE 5 A
GREAT PERSON
[ABE]
All right, listen up, everyone!
The culture festival's
in two weeks.
[MIRU]
Oh, yeah!
[TONBO] About time something
fun happened around this place!
But don't forget what the next
three days have in store!
Midterms!
[SHIRAISHI] Finally gives us
one second of joy--
[TAO]
Only to tear it away.
Just make sure to study,
and you won't have to worry
about missing the festival.
-Good luck!
-Aw, midterms suck.
I hate Math.
I didn't take notes.
Not like it would've helped ya!
[chuckles]
Yeah?
Not like you're one to talk!
[AYUMI]
Ah? What's up?
Uh...I'm happy
to lend you my notes.
Or, if it would help,
-we could study together?
-Uh!
[UKA] Well...
I'd like to if you would.
-[UKA] I mean--
-[SATORU] We studying?
Let's go to a diner!
[Ayumi gasps]
[screams]
[Uka gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
♪
-Soda, please!
-Doria for me.
You're up.
-Nankotsu.
-[UKA] Oh, no.
I didn't know
Miura was coming, too.
[AYUMI]
I'm gonna grab my drink.
-I'll join you.
-[AYUMI] No way!
-Stay put!
-[Uka trembling]
♪
[UKA]
What should I say?
Come on, think!
"This morning
my egg had two yolks!"
Cringe.
"So, you and Kanno
used to go out."
"So...you went
to the same school."
No good.
All I can think about
is the two of them together.
But I shouldn't bring it up.
I can't.
[NOA]
Got a table for us?
[WAITRESS 5A]
How many in your party?
You need your eyes checked?
Four of us, thank you.
[WAITRESS 5A]
Party of four.
Right this way.
♪
Huh?
Hm?
Isn't that guy Serina's ex?
♪
[UKA]
Ayumi wasn't kidding.
It is awkward.
Aw, look!
Let's sit here!
-Hold on.
-So, is it true, Miura?
Did you actually
go out with Serina?
Talk to us!
I wanna hear
all about the split!
[MEGU]
He's ignoring us? What a laugh!
[RINO]
Hey, why don't you tell us?
[SATORU]
Don't know, don't care.
[NOA] A little tea
never killed anyone.
Out of the loop
on that one, for real.
Sorry, Serina,
we can change tables.
[NOA]
We'll just follow you!
-Ah?
-Think we should bounce?
I don't think
Uka has enough time
to go somewhere else.
It's getting kinda late.
[NOA]
Got plans?
Well, my curfew's at 5:00.
[ALL]
Uh...
-[all laughing]
-You're kidding, that early?
Do your parents
have to put you in bubble wrap
so you don't hurt yourself?
-So cute!
-Does baby need her mommy?
[MEGU]
C'mon, who is she, anyway?
[RINO]
Does she even go to our school?
[NOA]
Loser!
-Lay off her.
-You're with him?
Do you expect
anyone to believe that?
I was gonna say!
Everyone's laughing at you!
[NOA]
Can you even tell?
[RINO]
She's so lame.
I almost feel bad!
♪
Didn't you hear me?
Lay off!
[gasps]
What's your deal?
[RINO] [scoffs]
Whatever.
Have it your way.
Ooh, that's good!
You're tellin' me!
They've been pissin'
me off all year long!
They're noisy in class
when I'm trying to work,
and they're always rude
when we go out!
[SERINA] They try to play
cute and say, "What a laugh."
Well, who's laughing now, huh?
[sighs]
I should go.
Hey, I'm sorry!
And thanks!
Uh, no.
I'm the one who's sorry.
Don't let what those
dumb jerks said get to you.
[UKA]
What?
Why is she apologizing to me?
Your name's Uka, right?
Let's chat sometime.
♪
[trickling]
Serina's always
been a real one, huh?
Mm-hm.
[UKA]
Kanno's awesome.
She stood up for me
without hesitation,
even though we're strangers.
Just like Miura.
♪
[water splashing]
[metal clanking]
[Rino and Megu chuckles]
[NOA]
That's payback for yesterday.
So, somethin'
you wanna say to us?
Don't forget, we were the ones
who were cool enough
to let you in our group.
Don't remember signing up.
[UKA]
Is she okay?
[SERINA]
The way I see it,
you got a girl
who's actually popular,
and I got three rats
chasing my crumbs.
[gasps]
Well, if that's how it is,
why don't you hang out
with that loser
Ishimori from now on?
[slaps]
♪
[grunts]
[SERINA]
Uh, what?
Uka?
I am okay!
I'm used to it!
Uh?
All of this started
because of my curfew!
Kanno was just
standing up for me!
If you wanna make
fun of me, go ahead!
-[MEGU] Chill.
-Please, just unload!
[KAI]
You're scaring them.
Tough luck.
Looks like you're in trouble
with "that loser Ishimori."
[KAI]
"Can you even tell?"
"I almost feel bad."
[all sigh]
-[all gasp]
-Okay, let's get outta here.
[indistinct chatter]
[NOA]
You're dead to me!
[MALE STUDENT 5D]
Don't be embarrassing.
[KAI]
Call me for help next time.
Serina.
[gasps]
♪
[footfall]
[SERINA] Hey,
I was doing fine without you!
Kai, slow down!
[TOMOYA]
Uka, your face all right?
Yeah, I'm fine!
Please don't worry about me!
♪
[UKA]
I can't ask.
I won't.
What's between them
is none of my business.
[AYUMI]
Even I don't know why!
[SATORU] Out of the loop
on that one, for real.
[UKA]
I can't make them tell me.
Apparently...no one can.
But it's clear
who should be at his side.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
GREETER
[UKA]
Good morning, everyone.
You need a little
pep in your step!
Good morning, everyone!
[SATORU]
Good morning, or somethin'.
Hey, isn't Miura here yet?
I told him what time
he was starting.
[TOMOYA]
Ah, speaking of.
-[UKA] A sweater.
-[TOMOYA] Good morning.
[UKA]
That's a new look.
Look who's late again!
Oh?
And where'd your hoodie go?
[KAI]
Lay off me.
[ABE]
Here, put it on.
[groans]
That looks so wrong on you!
Name anyone
who makes these look good.
♪
[UKA]
I hope Kanno's all right
considering what
happened yesterday.
[NOA]
Hi, Serina.
Huh?
Did you finish
the language homework?
Let's check each other's later!
Huh?
-Huh?
-Ah?
[MEGU]
Hey, Ishimori!
Sorry about yesterday!
[NOA]
You all good, now?
[RINO]
We're so sorry.
We all felt real bad
about that.
[MEGU]
It went a little far!
I mean, think about it.
Your curfew's nice!
The fact they want you back
at 5:00 just goes to show
how much your parents
care about you.
We were a little jealous,
and got carried away.
So, anyway, sorry.
You didn't do
anything wrong at all.
[UKA] Oh, thanks.
[MEGU] Ugh, got that over with!
[SERINA]
They're always like this.
[groans]
[AYUMI] And you still wanna be
friends with them, Serina?
You know, they're not all bad.
Promise.
I'd rather like them
than hate them,
so I try to make it work.
Still...I'm so glad
they gave you an apology
after the way they treated you.
Sorry you were caught
in the middle of that.
It's my fault.
[panting]
[both laughing]
-[SERINA] Oh, right. Kai!
-Hm?
[SERINA] Can I give you
your hoodie back tomorrow?
Just whenever you can.
[SERINA] I'll make sure
to wash it first.
[UKA] All that awkwardness
went away overnight.
I wonder what'll happen if they
keep getting close like this.
♪
Hmm.
[AYUMI]
Something wrong, Yuru?
You know, something's been
on my mind for a while now!
[YURU] Hm!
I wanna give Uka a ponytail!
Ahh.
[YURU]
Promise you'll look cute!
[gasps]
Ta-dah!
[AYUMI]
Ah!
-Everyone, look!
-[SATORU] What the hell?
Why are they freaking out
like they found a dead body?
[UKA] When's the last time
I put up my hair?
I can't remember.
It's a little embarrassing.
Is this look okay on me?
[gasps]
Makin' friends like a pro.
Honestly,
you'd do fine without me.
♪
[UKA]
What does he mean by that?
Maybe he doesn't want me
around anymore?
♪
[MIZOGUCHI] Okay,
pay attention to this one.
Excuse me, teach!
What do we need
to know for test day?
As long as you've been
taking notes, you'll be fine.
[TONBO] You know I'm not paying
enough attention for that!
Someone! Save me!
[MIZOGUCHI]
There's no saving you.
Come on, don't get mad!
[MIZOGUCHI]
How would you feel if no one
paid attention to you?
It's fine!
[bell chiming]
-Let's go to the store.
-Yeah!
-[UKA] Excuse me!
-Uh?
Here!
Copy mine!
-Ah!
-[both groan
Ah, whoops.
We weren't serious.
We don't actually care
how we do on the test.
More like we're just
ridin' the vibe
with the teach, ya know?
[gasps]
"Vibe?"
Watch it, Tonbo.
Don't use words
like that around her.
You think Ishimori even
understands what vibes are?
But, hey,
thanks a bunch for the offer!
Not like we were gonna
study anyway.
♪
[UKA]
Guess I messed up again.
I'll take ya there sometime!
We could go this weekend,
if you're free.
♪
[UKA]
"Vibe.
A person's emotional state
or the mood of the room."
♪
I kinda understand,
but I kinda don't.
I wonder if it's wrong
to even look it up.
Like it's something
I'm supposed to just get.
[all laughing]
[UKA]
Something's wrong with me.
[KAMAKIRI] Don't ya think
Serina's mad hot?
And she always smells so good.
So?
Spill it.
Why'd you break up?
Tell us!
Or we can all take guesses,
and see who gets it right.
[YASUSHI]
Oh! One of 'em cheated!
-They couldn't get along!
-Kai played it too cool!
There it is!
"I can't really tell
if you care about me!
You never let me know
what's going on in your head!"
Like that?
Gotta be!
It's so like Kai!
You're way too cold.
[MIRU]
Like, dude...
you ever tell a girl you
like her, or you're jealous?
Once or twice.
-Hm?
-[MIRU] Oh?
♪
[UKA]
Once or twice?
♪
Yeah, sure.
It must be something
only Kanno gets to see.
A different side to him.
Just for her.
A side I'll never witness.
[gasps]
-Nap time.
-Hm?
[UKA] I'll wake you up
when the bell rings.
[KAI] [sighs]
Thanks.
♪
[UKA]
Is this it?
Is this how he sees me?
[clock ticking]
That's fine.
At least, it means
I'm useful to him.
Tell me...
when you got slapped yesterday,
you mentioned something
about being "used to it."
Were you being literal?
Uh?
Oh, no.
I'd never actually gotten
slapped in the face before.
[KAI] [sighs]
Good.
[UKA]
Another mistake.
I made him worry over nothing.
[gasps]
It's swollen.
Must've hurt.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[KAI]
You're bright red.
Well, wake me when it's time.
[sighs]
[UKA]
Whoa!
Where did any
of that come from?
Miura's hand was...
Wait!
First, remember,
you have to breathe!
Nope! Freaking out!
[deep breathing]
[UKA]
Sorry, I'll be back.
[footfall]
[door opens and closes]
[UKA]
Why do I react like this?
Am I the only one?
I'm reading too much into it.
It wasn't a big deal to him.
Miura lives in a completely
different world from me.
One with everyone else in it.
And I might never reach.
[MEGU]
Hey, Ishimori!
-See Kai?
-Uh.
No.
[sighs]
Like I thought.
[NOA] We're not
in the same class as him,
so how are we
supposed to chat
if he's not around
during breaks?
[MEGU] [sighs]
Bummer.
[RINO]
Where do ya think he went?
Is it safe to say you know?
-Ah!
-[chuckles]
If I were gonna bet,
then I'd guess the storage room
on the fourth floor!
Of course, you don't
have to confirm that!
Amazing!
You know him so well!
You're right!
[chuckles]
[UKA]
Just goes to show it, though.
No one's closer to Miura
than she is.
So, he still runs off
to empty rooms
to take his naps, huh?
-Has he always done that?
-Yep.
He would ask me to watch him
sleep on the roof.
And I'm like, how'd he manage
to open the door?
The thing was locked!
Hey, didn't he say
to keep it a secret, though?
I think you're
the exception, Kanno.
What is that supposed to mean?
I'll just pretend
like you never told me!
Also, don't use "Kanno."
Just call me Serina!
[gasps]
♪
[UKA]
"Serina."
She is amazing.
Cute and tough.
And yet...so gentle.
Honestly?
Seeing all this reminds me
of junior high.
You're the same as me!
We even got the same
"no blabbing" rule.
[chuckles]
But he never asked me
to join him up there.
I just randomly found out.
I'm not anything like you.
You're too good
to compare yourself to me.
[sighs]
[gasps]
[UKA] Oh, I made it
hard for her to respond.
She feels bad because of me.
Yeah.
I'm a nuisance to others.
I need to change that, too.
But how can I
when I'm constantly
putting myself down?
I want to embrace my new life.
But how can I,
when I do...this?
-[UKA] Um, sorry--
-[MALE STUDENT 5E] Serina!
Hey, girl.
Care to explain this?
Excuse me?
Why do you have a picture
of your ex on your phone?
[SERINA] More like, why are
you looking without asking?
How'd you even
get my phone open?
[MIHO] Sorry.
Didn't know
they were
looking over my shoulder.
[MALE STUDENT 5F]
Well, speak of the devil,
and he shall appear!
Look at what I found!
Looks like someone wants
to come crawling back to you!
Hey, no!
You should give her
another chance!
[YURU] I've got the same pic
in my phone, you know.
-Huh?
-[YURU] We all do.
[YURU] It's supposed
to make you popular.
[MALE STUDENT 5F]
Who'd spread a rumor like that?
When we all first
saw the yearbook,
the girls thought Kai's photo
was way too pretty,
and we wished we could have one
half as good as that.
So, we snapped a pic or two,
'cause, hey.
Maybe it'll make us
gals prettier!
Yeah, so I took the picture and
gave it to the rest of them.
[SERINA]
Here, thanks again.
So, I can just get
a person's qualities
if I keep a picture of them?
In that case,
I want one of Serina!
She's gorg.
Then, I ought to grab
one of Takamine.
Ayumi's would work, too.
She's cute.
I want more friends,
so I'll take Seto.
So what's your trait?
[gasps]
[MIHO]
From your picture?
[MIHO] Ishimori--
[KAI] Self-doubting.
That's a little harsh.
[KAI]
Anxious.
Thinks too much.
Martyr.
Honest.
Caring.
-[sighs]
-[KAI] Courageous.
♪
Now leave.
Get one of Tomoya.
Yeah, let's go, Serina.
Bossy.
[KAI]
And, too self-deprecating.
-[KAI] Yuru.
-Hm?
[KAI] Do her hair
like this again sometime.
That mean she actually
likes it this way?
No clue.
I'm saying I like it.
[gasps]
♪
[yawns]
Back to sleep.
[trembling]
[UKA]
I can't stand.
Not after that.
[KAI]
Honest.
[whimpering]
Caring.
♪
Courageous.
[UKA]
I know he's right.
I am courageous...
because I love him.
[UKA]
I'm exactly where I need to be.
I want to do more than study.
I can't keep writing things off
as beyond my depth.
Well, the midterms
are now safely behind us.
So, I hope you're ready
for the culture festival!
First, let's select someone
as our committee member.
Any volunteers?
[SHIRAISHI]
Sounds super boring.
[TAO] How can you ask
without explaining what it is?
♪
-Huh?
-[UKA] I volunteer.
[UKA]
Please, let me!
I'll try anything I can.
Anything new.
[indistinct chatter]
Until that one day...
when I can finally
be their equal.
TO BE CONTINUED